<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on daylin morgan</title>
    <link>https://dayl.in/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on daylin morgan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dayl.in/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I used bibtex and python to automatically generate my publications page</title>
      <link>https://dayl.in/posts/publications-how-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dayl.in/posts/publications-how-to/</guid>
      <description>Basic Workflow  Generate bibtex using references managed in Zotero Parse and edit metadata as necessary Write markdown documents for each entry in bibtex Transfer these documents to the content/publications directory Generate a list page for each article grouped and ordered by year   The central goal of this script is to take a bibtex file and automatically generate a requisite markdown document per article with the necessary front matter to generate my publications page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How I adapted Hugo to build and style my personal website</title>
      <link>https://dayl.in/posts/hugo-theme-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 12:38:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dayl.in/posts/hugo-theme-setup/</guid>
      <description>In order to personalize the theme I chose for my website, I initially forked the project on github and placed it in the themes/ directory of my website repo using git submodule add. I made a few minor changes to the html&amp;rsquo;s and css, but ultimately decided it would be simpler to leave the theme repo in the same state as it&amp;rsquo;s main repo. Hugo gives priority to the layouts found in the parent directory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://dayl.in/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 18:44:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dayl.in/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is an initial test of Hugo as a static site generator. So far it feels more powerful and polished than pelican. My next posts will explore the ways in which I have adapted Hugo and the theme coder-portfolio to my needs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
