<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>daylin morgan</title>
    <link>https://dayl.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on daylin morgan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 12:38:07 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dayl.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How I adapted Hugo to build and style my personal website</title>
      <link>https://dayl.in/posts/hugo-theme-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 12:38:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dayl.in/posts/hugo-theme-setup/</guid>
      <description>In order to personalize the theme I chose for my website, I initially forked the project on github and placed it in the themes/ directory of my website repo using git submodule add. I made a few minor changes to the html&amp;rsquo;s and css, but ultimately decided it would be simpler to leave the theme repo in the same state as it&amp;rsquo;s main repo. Hugo gives priority to the layouts found in the parent directory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>https://dayl.in/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 18:44:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dayl.in/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>This is an initial test of Hugo as a static site generator. So far it feels more powerful and polished than pelican. My next posts will explore the ways in which i have adatpted Hugo and the theme coder-portfolio to my needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://dayl.in/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dayl.in/about/</guid>
      <description>As an engineer, I am constantly in awe of the systems we find in nature.
My current works involves using synthetic biolgy and next-generation sequencing to interrogate sub-population growth and drug response dynamics in TNBC. This is carried out in the Brock Lab at the Univeristy of Texas at Austin. You can see more of this and previous work here.
In my spare time, I foray into various programming projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
